ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: LABOR UNITY
  - Local 14J Toronto Xerox. (Box 9, Folder 74)
    Includes: collective bargaining class.
  - Local 36 West Bank Community Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 9, Folder 75)
    Includes: CDC workers
  - Local 55D Zodys. (Box 9, Folder 76)
    Includes: L.A. 4.86 job placement workshop; negotiating committee, Southern Cal. Jt. Bd.
  - Local 87 (Double Springs, Alabama)., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    Includes: Christmas Party 12/16/97
  - Local 90., 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff78 Includes: work seminar Knoxville Fall, 1978; check presentation
  - Local 95- Cowden Manufacturing. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff79 Includes: contact sheet
  - Local 99. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff80 Includes: discussion; strike, Uniontown, KY, Kentucky Cap. Co.; picketing Hygiene Industries L.A.
  - Local 82 Arlington Hats. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff81 Includes: voting; negotiating; committee
  - Local 107. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff82 Includes: officer installation
  - Local 119a. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff83 Includes: Mauro DeFazio, Albert and Katherine Joseph, Al Boandl
  - Local 128. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff84 Includes: group shot
  - Local 129H Garland Texas. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff85 Includes: officers and stewards
  - Local 146 (Shoe Workers). (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff86 Includes: negotiating committee
  - Local 147G (Knoxville Glove Co.). (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff87 Includes negotiators
  - Local 155 U.S. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff88 Includes: picketing Sterling Plastics Co. West St. Paul, Minn.
  - Local 165 (Shoe). (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff89 Includes: group shot
  - Local 166. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff90 Includes: portrait of member; picket. D.B. Rosenblatt Co. plant, Minneapolis
  - Local 188. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff91 Includes: Washougal, Wash. Shop steward training, Pendleton Woolen Mills
  - Local 195 (H and P Industries) Franklin, Wisc. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff92 Includes: group shot
  - Local 207 (Buffalo). (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff93 Includes: Edward Salva
  - Local 210 Florsheim Shoe Co. (Poplar Bluff, MO). (Box 35, Folder 17)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff94 Includes: veteran ceremony
  - Local 213. (Box 35, Folder 18)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff95 Includes: science fair, Dunkirk, NY; Buffalo Jt. Bd.
  - Local 226C., 1987 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff96 Includes: officers, Americus, GA. 4/87; gavel presentation
  - Local 233 (Canada). (Box 35, Folder 20)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff97 Includes: Carol Flaxman replaces Steve Lytwyn
  - Local 234a (Vandalia, Ill.). (Box 35, Folder 21)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff98 Includes: check presentation
  - Local 238a (Shoe). (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff99 Includes: Fun-Shoe Ltd. Agreement
  - Local 246 Shirt and Leisurewear. (Box 35, Folder 23)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff100 Includes: HAP counselor
  - Local 254c (St. Louis, MO). (Box 35, Folder 24)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff101 Includes: officer installation
  - Local 267. (Box 35, Folder 25)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff102 Includes: executive board installation
  - Local 274 (Canada)., 1991 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff103 Includes: executives; 60th Anniversary Party 11/28/91
  - Local 281. (Box 35, Folder 27)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff104 Includes: leadership training session; Bemis, TN; celebrating raise; Tennessee Textiles, Jackson, TN
  - Local 283 (San Diego). (Box 35, Folder 28)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff105 Includes: picnic
  - Local 303b (Kitchener, Ontario)., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff106 Includes: John Forsyth Co. workers awards banquet 4/26/86
  - Local 303t (Arrow Co Kitchener, Ontario). (Box 35, Folder 30)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff107 Includes: Gerber cutting machine
  - Local 305 TWVA., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff108 Includes 1/76 conference speech Don Nolette
  - Local 314. (Box 35, Folder 32)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff109 Includes: Arrow Co leafleting.
  - Local 317t Front Royal, VA. (Box 35, Folder 33)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff110 Includes: vice-president
  - Local 335t Kenro Co. Fredonia, Wisc. (Box 35, Folder 34)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff111 Includes: negotiators, Pat Cronin
  - Local 340 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    Collection was re-organized, this was formerly box 9, ff 112
  - Local 340a (Baron's Dept. Stores Smithtown, NY). (Box 35, Folder 36)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff113 Includes signing contract.
  - Local 365 Arrow Shirt (Atlanta GA)., 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff114 Includes: Exec. Bd. 11/1/86 w/ Wyche Fowler; Lucy Willis, union president; Cluett locals; Strategy Sessions in Southern locals 11/87
  - Local 406. (Box 35, Folder 38)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff115 Includes Biddleford, ME. Scholars; Maine Jt. Bd. Scholarships
  - Local 420 (Hanover, PA)., 1982 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff116 Includes L. 419 woman w/ grandsons, Everett, PA; July 1982 L.420 women w/ 4th of July cake
  - Local 438. (Box 35, Folder 40)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff117 Includes Whiting contract
  - Local 454 Bluebird Fabric (York, PA). (Box 35, Folder 41)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff118 Includes: check presentation
  - Local 455 Breman, GA. (Box 35, Folder 42)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff119 Includes: women
  - Local 459 (Canada). (Box 35, Folder 43)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff120 Includes steward training.
  - Local 473. (Box 35, Folder 44)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff121 Includes: back pay, Ellen, NC
  - Local 487 Textile. (Box 35, Folder 45)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff122 Includes: Columbus, Ohio officer installation; Columbus, Ohio Joint COPE committee area locals; two-day training institute Columbus, Ohio, locals; Columbus Control, Fraternity Sportswear, Ketchup Distributors
  - Local 496 - Louisville, Kentucky (Box 35, Folder 46)
    Collection was re-organized, this was formerly box 9, ff 123
  - Local 500 Motley Shirt (Dover, NJ). (Box 35, Folder 47)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff124 Includes: shirt and leisurewear picnic
  - Local 568 Risto, Inc.. (Box 35, Folder 48)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff125 Includes: negotiating team
  - Local 573 Bradshaw Co. (Box 35, Folder 49)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff126 Includes: negotiation team
  - Local 615 Health Tex. (Box 35, Folder 50)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff127 Includes: demonstration, Health-Tex Hdq Central Falls, R.I.; scholarship awards
  - Local 641a Hyde Park Glove Co. (Box 35, Folder 51)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff128 Includes: party, pendant presentation
  - Local 657., 1982 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff129 Includes: 11/2/82/ audience at meeting
  - Local 673. (Box 35, Folder 53)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff130 Includes: donation to Heart Fund, Groutsville MD
  - Local 675, Newberry, SC fair. (Box 35, Folder 54)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff131 Includes: oldest member; group shot; performance
  - Local 687 J. Ensign Bickford. - Not in box at re-housing (Box 35, Folder 55)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff132 Includes: Simsbury, CT contract signing
  - Local 689. (Box 35, Folder 56)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff133 Includes: Rome, Georgia new officers
  - Local 704c. (Box 35, Folder 57)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff134 Includes: Danville, VA Christmas parade; Little Mr. And Miss. ACTWV contest, union hall
  - Local 708., 1981 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff135 Includes: 12/8/81 Columbia, Miss. Officer installation
  - Local 723t (Texflex). (Box 35, Folder 59)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff136 Includes: comp check
  - Local 730d (Bayle Corp-Visalia, CA)., 1982 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff137 Includes: Chuck Sheppard speech 11/3/82
  - Local 740. (Box 35, Folder 61)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff138 Includes: negotiating committee; Guelph, Ontario strike; strike Rene Industries Western Ontario Jt. Bd.
  - Local 799 (Warren, Ark.) Jack Winter, Inc., 1981 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff139 Includes: Christmas party for retarded children 1970s; "Save Atlanta Children" Day 4/25/81
  - Local 800 (New Haven). (Box 35, Folder 63)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff140 Includes: Consolidated Laundries, New Haven; check presentation, Cecil Toppin, Benjamin Spindel; Springfield and Hartford CT members in shop
  - Local 818 Stillman Seal Co. (Box 35, Folder 64)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff141 Includes: Carlsbad, CA Neg. Comm.
  - Local 822 Armstrong Cork. (Box 35, Folder 65)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff142 Includes: silver tankards, Jt Bd Mtg
  - Local 844. (Box 35, Folder 66)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff143 Includes: stewards
  - Local 865. Jasper, Ala. (Box 35, Folder 67)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff144 Includes: ambulance funds
  - Local 873- Prattsville, Alabama. (Box 35, Folder 68)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff145 Includes: group shot
  - Local 906 Clarksvilee, Tenn. (Box 35, Folder 69)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff146 Includes: group shots
  - Local 914. (Box 35, Folder 70)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff147 Includes: union hall, Pelahatchie, Miss. Officer installation
  - Local 924 Evergreen, AL Lady Arrow. (Box 35, Folder 71)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff148 Includes: members, back pay check
  - Local 931., 1987 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff149 Includes: German trade unionists tour Rector Sportswear, Rector, AK 9/87; float in parade; women at work
  - Local 937 Corah. (Box 35, Folder 73)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff150 Includes: Vera Lees, Annalea Watson, Monty Davidson
  - Local 939t (Versailles, CT) Amstar Corp. (Box 35, Folder 74)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff151 Includes: negotiations
  - Local 953 Bemis (St. Louis). (Box 35, Folder 75)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff152 Includes: union charity
  - Local 958. (Box 35, Folder 76)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff153 Includes: plaque presentation, Ethican L. 958, Chicago
  - Local 972. (Box 35, Folder 77)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff154 Includes: Devton Mills, Centerville Michigan, L. 972c
  - Local 981. (Box 35, Folder 78)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff155 Includes: Findlay Industries shop
  - Local 992. (Box 35, Folder 79)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff156 Includes: Lady Arrow settlement, Brantley, Ala.
  - Local 1016 (Manchester, NH) Armtec., 1981 (Box 35, Folder 80)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff157 Includes: 7/81 group shot
  - Local 1018., 1987 (Box 35, Folder 81)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff158 Includes: press conference; retiree dinner 8/87
  - Local 1021c Anniston Sportswear. (Box 35, Folder 82)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff159 Includes cerebral palsy fund-raiser
  - Local 1034., 1983 (Box 35, Folder 83)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff160 Includes: Huntington, PA Owens Coring Fiberglass 5/1983 officer installation L. 1034-7
  - Local 1036T. (Box 35, Folder 84)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff161
  - Local 1038c Reltoc Co. (Box 35, Folder 85)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff162 Includes: union officers
  - Local 1046., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 86)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff163 Includes: scholarship winners, Salisbury, MD 1986
  - Local 1055 Opelika Mfg. Co. (Box 35, Folder 87)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff164 Includes: retirement party
  - Local 1060 (Guelph, Ontario). (Box 35, Folder 88)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff165 Includes: Rennie Industries; sock turning machine, Jack Postelthwaite Bud Clark
  - Local 1067c (Ciales, Puerto Rico) Hathaway. (Box 35, Folder 89)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff166 Includes: sign agreement
  - Local 1075 Enro Shirt Co., 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 90)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff167 Includes: new officers and stewards for Woodruff, SC local, 1979; 1975 group shot
  - Local 1077. (Box 35, Folder 91)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff168 Includes: school in Whiteville, N.C.
  - Local 1085. (Box 35, Folder 92)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff169 Includes: parade float; handshake; contract signing with Columbian Rope Co.
  - Local 1086 M.W. Jeans (Donnacona, Quebec). (Box 35, Folder 93)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff170 Includes: meeting
  - Local 1093T., 1978-1986 (Box 35, Folder 94)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff171 Includes: Rock Hill, SC, Celanese Corp. negotiations June 1986; training; New Celanese agreement; leadership meeting; 7/78 Stetin meets w/ L.1093t
  - Local 1113t. (Box 35, Folder 95)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff172 Includes: Cove Granite Finishing Co., speech
  - Local 1120., 1957-1975 (Box 35, Folder 96)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff173 Includes: Senior Citizens Valentine location, Orangeburg, SC; 2/15/75 celebration; 4/57 seniors
  - Local 1134 (Technofil Inc.) Laurierville, Quebec. (Box 35, Folder 97)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff174 Includes: new contract
  - Local 1142 San Antonio, Texas. (Box 35, Folder 98)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff175 Includes: "union baby," baby w/ button
  - Local 1144. (Box 35, Folder 99)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff176 Includes (Hispanic) locals 544, 885, 1143, 1144, 1131
  - Local 1147. (Box 35, Folder 100)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff177 Includes: Orangeburg, SC Jeansville Corp., negotiating team
  - Local 1148c., 1988 (Box 35, Folder 101)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff178 Includes: check presentation on from L. 563; Laurel, Miss. Home destroyed by tornado; president 1148-T, Yocom Knitting, Stowe, PA, Mid-Atlantic conf. 11/88
  - Local 1149 J Besner and Sons. (Box 35, Folder 102)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff179 Includes: agreement renewal, Cornwall, Ontario, negotiating committee, employees, Saul Linds
  - Local 1156t., 1977 (Box 35, Folder 103)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff180 Includes: Willimantic, Conn. Agreement signing, 10/83 Brand-Rex co.; signing contract with Brand-Rex; signing 1977
  - Local 1198t Wardwell Braid Central Falls, RI. (Box 35, Folder 104)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff181 Includes: contract signing, union bargaining committee, management representatives, '85
  - Local 1209t. (Box 35, Folder 105)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff182 Includes: Fall River L. 1209 T strike
  - Local 1259., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 106)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff183 Includes: Munsingwear Co., Ashland, WI, grievance settlement, July 1986
  - Local 1300. (Box 35, Folder 107)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff184 Includes: Woodstock, meeting, officers and stewards
  - Local 1305 Fiberglass Corning ware., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 108)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff185 Includes: cheque presentation, 1976; delegates, buzz group exercise, Leadership Skills conference, Kitchener; conference discussion, Kitchener
  - Local 1340 Midwest Handbag. (Box 35, Folder 109)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff186 Includes: discussion and to re-open, (black) family
  - Local 1355. (Box 35, Folder 110)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b 9, ff187 Includes: Fletcher, NC, Cranston Print Works Company, newly elected officers
  - Local 1386. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 188 Includes: stewards
  - Local 1406., 1979-1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 189 Includes: Sponge Inc., 1982 pack signing, Cleveland; 1979 Sponge, Inc. negotiators sign
  - Local 1414C Xerox (California). (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 190 Includes group shot; woman
  - Local 1414D Xerox. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 191 Includes: safety, Oklahoma City Xerox; safety award, Xerox
  - Local 1414F "Loral" (Los Angeles). (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 192 Includes: Loral Corp. members at ratification meeting
  - Local 1419 (Valleyfield, Quebec). (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 193 Includes: negotiating team
  - Local 1422. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 194 Includes: Janesville Products ground-breaking, Ohio
  - Local 1426 Bemis Bags., 1977-1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 195 Includes pact-signing, Terre Haute, Ind. 1977, Charles Sallee; Finley tours Bemis Bag 1981; picket line 1985, Bemis strike
  - Local 1436 Bedford, VA Chevron Inc. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 196 Includes: officer installation
  - Local 1441 Centex Mills. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 197 Includes: sign agreement
  - Local 1448. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 198 Includes: Phoenix Dyeworks, Cleveland, Ohio contract
  - Local 1495 (Steams and Foster)., 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 199 Includes: 3/76, contract signing; 1979 contract signing
  - Local 1536. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 200 Includes: John Reed, president
  - Local 1549. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 201 Includes: Cedartown, GA classes for L. 1549 and 943, Alton Box Board and Alton Tube Division, negatives
  - Local 1559 (Pine Grove)., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 202 Includes: contracts, PA. 1978
  - Local 1585. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 203 Includes: L. 1585-1, Tapis Peerless signing; L. 1585-2 Tapis Peerless signing; L. 1576 Tapis signing; L. 1585-1, shearing machine operator; L. 15546 strike Fiskeville, RI Arkwright, Inc.; Acton Vale, Que. L. 1585
  - Local 1591. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 204 Includes: striking Stewart Group workers, L. 1591 of Greater Toronto Textile Jt. BD.; Bud Clark visits ultra-modern textile mill, Markham, Ohio
  - Local 1604., 1976 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 205 Includes: 1976; Canton Mills agrees on strike cotton dust measures; OSHA at Canton Mills; community building L. 1604; speech; Canton, GA retiree officers sworn in
  - Local 1619 (Montreal)., 1981 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 206 Includes: negotiating committee, Summer 1981, Consul conjoint du Quebec
  - Local 1629., 1982 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 207 Includes: meeting; strikers at Nalpac Ltd. 1982
  - Local 1633., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 208 Includes: Alton Box Board Co., Paper tube Division, Mobile, Ala. 1978, double checking contract
  - Local 1637. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 209 Includes: Gerry Packenberg, Maurice Robillard, Arthur Dollock Canada
  - Local 1664 Consolidated Textiles., 1978-1986 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 210 Includes: contract signing, Consoltex Inc., Alexandria, Ont. Negotiating team, 1986; 1978 Consolidated Textiles contract signing Alexandria, Ont.
  - Local 1669. (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 211 Includes: J. Bass contract
  - Local 1699 (Compagnie Conso- Graber). (Box 36, Folder 25)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 212 Includes: Montreal, negotiating committee
  - Local 1701 Puritan Spts. Duncansville, PA., 1987 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 213 Includes: 1987 Neg. Committee
  - Local 1703 (Chicago, Ill.). (Box 36, Folder 27)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 214
  - Local 1714T Sealy. (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 215 Includes: group shot
  - Local 1734. (Box 36, Folder 29)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 216 Includes: group shot
  - Local 1739., 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 217 Includes: Masland Carpet Co., Carlisle PA, 1986 sign pact; arbitration award, CH. Masland and Sons, 1986; 1987 Bruce Dunton presents award; 1985 Stewards class, Vastina Wilson
  - Local 1742., 1976-1982 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 218 Includes: examining Tennessee State Court Order, 1982; 1976 negotiating committee
  - Local 1742 GA-TN-AL Joint Board, Shop Steward Classes. (Box 36, Folder 32)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 219 Includes: Knoxville Stewards classes; GTA Joint Board
  - Local 1748., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 220 Includes: Buffalo, NY, Curbell Inc. strikers collect money for crippled children drive, 1978
  - Local 1751T Cranston Print Works., 1989 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 221 Includes: Webster, MA 1989 strike
  - Local 1752 Alton Packaging., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 222 Includes: negotiating team, 1977, Mountain Home, NC
  - Local 1756., 1979-1983 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 223 Includes: St. Hyacinthe and Canada U.S. Knits, Que. Local 1756 1983; 1979 agreement, Canadian U.S. Knitting Mills
  - Local 1779 (Courtaulds)., 1979-1981 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 224 Includes: 1979 negotiators; 1981 negotiators
  - Local 1781 Eslon., 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 225 Includes: ratification meeting, Hordis Brothers, Jan. 18 1987; Hordis Brothers negotiating committee; Elson strike; Rock Hill, SC workshop, Stablex hazardous waste processing plant workers, 1985
  - Local 1786., 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 226 Includes: 1977 negotiating committee, Mantex Ltd.; 1978 negotiating committee Mantex
  - Local 1797 (Canvil Co.- Canada)., 1982 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 227 Includes: Acton Valley, Que. New agreement signed by negotiating committee 1982
  - Local 1800. (Box 36, Folder 41)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 228 Includes: Boise Cascade, Rochester, NY, new officers
  - Local 1813. (Box 36, Folder 42)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 229 Includes: Paramount Industries, Don Lee Plastics, sign agreement
  - Local 1816. (Box 36, Folder 43)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 230 Includes: contract signing, Kayser- Roth, London, Ontario
  - Local 1826 (R-M Industrial Products). (Box 36, Folder 44)
    Collection re-housed, formerly b9, ff 231 Includes: North Charleston, SC, waiting for picket duty at union hall
  - Local 1831 Barre, VT., 1984 (Box 36, Folder 45)